Hello, I am Savita Maiti,
an advisor [ __ ] product
trainer at ICICI Potential Life Insurance Company. ICICI Life Insurance
Company has
come up with a new product in its birthday month, December, called
Signature
Assure. It is truly
unique. This
plan, like other ULI plans, can be
invested in equity funds, debt funds and balance funds.
To take this plan, you have to be between 18
and 50 years old. Those who are below 18 years old and
above 50 years old
cannot take this plan because in this case, the proposal is
not available. The person taking this plan has
life risk coverage.
PPT means premium paying
term is five to
15 years and PT means policy term is 20
years. This
plan is available for a minimum of 30,000 taka.
This plan is available for an annual of 30,000 taka. Let me explain
this plan with an example. Let me say that a
person of 30 years old takes this plan.
He took the plan and decided to
give one lakh rupees for five years, that is,
he will give five lakh rupees in five years.
After giving five lakh rupees, that is,
after five years, he can take maturity in 20 years. If
he wants,
he can also withdraw all the money including growth at any time after five years.
But if for some reason the
person dies unfortunately after paying a premium,
then
what will the nominee get? The nominee will
get 10 times the money immediately, that is, 10 lakh rupees, and along with that, he will get
one lakh rupees per year for the remaining 19 years, that is, 19 lakh
rupees,
and his remaining
premium will be web-based. He will not have to pay that.
The policy is active and finally,
after 20 years, he will
get maturity of about 27 lakh rupees, that is, his
nominee total will be about 56 lakh rupees.
In this case, the
return
money is exempted from ten percent and will not be taxable.
But yes, the nominee, but he will
not be able to withdraw the money whenever he wants,
but he will have to follow this rule.
This
was the
feature of this plan. I hope this is such a plan.  No
one in the insurance world has been able to bring what this
ICICI Prudence Life Insurance
Company has brought to us. I
hope I was able to explain the plan to everyone.
However, if anyone has any further questions,
please call me on 943417989.
Thank you.